Hi, this is Doreen with WTI.
So whether it's nice and the kids are out of school, are they bugging you to go fishing
but you don't want to spend a ton of money on fishing gear or you have very little idea
of fishing in general.
While the Plasano Kids Fishing Pole will save you a ton of time and money, I love that
it has a Telescoping rod so we're not in use it easily packs up and stores away in
the bag that it comes with.
The bright orange color also makes it very easy to spot and this length of 5.9 feet actually
means an adult can use it too.
It comes with a tackle box, soft lures, hooks, barbers, sinkers, everything you will need
to get started with fishing.
It also comes with a spin cast in reel which is very easy to use and the reel is
pre-spooled so you don't have to get tangled up with a fishing line when you are just getting
started.
Just attach your hook, bait and cast.
This fishing rod has made getting started fishing a breeze.
So don't hesitate to get this affordable Telescopic fishing rod from Plasano.
Get out there and start fishing and that's my point of view.